https://www.durhamfreemasons.org/cookies-policy/

Tel: 0191 567 5365
Follow Us:
Masonic Charitable Foundation
Important COVID-19 update from the Provincial Grand Master - Local Restrictions: 'click here'
Privacy Policy
What is this Privacy Policy for?
This privacy policy is for this website www.durhamfreemasons.org and governs the privacy of the users who choose to use it.
The policy sets out the different areas where user privacy is concerned and outlines the obligations and requirements of the users, the website and website owners. Furthermore, the way this website processes, stores and protects user data and information will also be detailed within this policy.
The Website
This website and its owners take a proactive approach to user privacy, and ensure the necessary steps are taken to protect the privacy of its users throughout their visiting experience. This website complies to all UK national laws and requirements for user privacy.
Use of Cookies
This website uses cookies to better the users experience while visiting the website. Where applicable, this website uses a cookie control system allowing the user on their first visit to the website to allow or disallow the use of cookies on their computer / device. This complies with legislation requirements for websites to obtain explicit consent from users before leaving behind or reading files such as cookies on a user’s computer / device.
Cookies are small files saved to the user’s device that track, save and store information about the user’s interactions and usage of the website. This allows the website, through its server, to provide the users with a tailored experience within this website.
Users are advised that if they wish to deny the use and saving of cookies from this website on to their computers hard drive, they should take necessary steps within their web browsers security settings to block all cookies from this website.
This website uses tracking software to monitor its visitors to better understand how they use it. This software is provided by Google Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage. The software will save a cookie to your device in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website, but will not store, save or collect personal information. You can read Google’s privacy policy here for further information http://www.google.com/privacy.html.
No personal information is stored, saved, or collected.
Contact & Communication
Users contacting this website and/or its owners do so at their own discretion and provide any such personal details requested at their own risk. Your personal information is kept private and stored securely until a time it is no longer required or has no use, as detailed in the Data Protection Act 1998. Every effort has been made to ensure a safe and secure form to email submission process but advise users using such form to email processes that they do so at their own risk.
This website and its owners use any information submitted solely to assist you in answering any questions or queries you may have submitted.
Your details are not passed on to any third parties.
IMAGE GALLERY
TLC Teddy Initiative……
“thank you Freemasons for the thousands of teddies donated to children’s casualty departments”
Community Support Grants…..
“The grant from Durham Freemasons has made an enormous difference to our service users”
Provincial Annual Meeting….
“The Provincial annual meeting is one of the highlights of my year, it’s great to meet everyone and support all those being rewarded for merit”….
Masonic Widows……
“My husband would be so proud that you still contact me so many years after his death, thank you for remembering me”
Provincial Meeting…..
“The Provincial annual meeting is one of the highlights of my year, it’s great to meet everyone and support all those being rewarded for merit”
The Royal Arch…..
“I feel that I have a much better understanding of the whole Masonic story after joining the Royal Arch”
What have you gained?
“I’ve made wonderful friendships with people from all walks of life who I wouldn’t otherwise have even met”
In respect to the TLC Teddy initiative
“A child patient copes with medical treatment so much better when they’ve been given a TLC teddy”
What Freemasonry has done for you?
“The teachings of the masonic ceremonies helped me to be a better father, better husband, better son and better neighbour”What Freemasonry has done for you
One of the best things I have ever done…
“Along with getting married, the birth of my children and Sunderland winning the FA Cup, becoming a Freemason is one of the best things I’ve ever done”
Latest News
view all >
3rd October 2020
A Message from the Provincial Grand Master
Read More
18th September 2020
COVID-19 Updates
Read More
Latest Tweets
Follow @twitter
Durham FreemasonsFollowThe Official Twitter feed of the Provincial Grand Lodge and Provincial Grand Chapter of DurhamDurham Freemasons@PGLDurham·23hDurham Freemasons
wish The Grand Master, HRH The Duke of Kent, a very happy birthday.
#DurhamFreemasons Reply on Twitter 1314498250397962240Retweet on Twitter 13144982503979622403Like on Twitter 13144982503979622406Twitter 1314498250397962240Durham Freemasons@PGLDurham·8 Octhttps://www.facebook.com/914169948737983/posts/1728153860672917/?extid=0&d=nReply on Twitter 1314284395285696514Retweet on Twitter 1314284395285696514Like on Twitter 13142843952856965141Twitter 1314284395285696514Load More...
Provincial Grand Lodge of Durham
8 The Esplanade
Sunderland
Tyne & Wear
SR2 7BH
Tel: 0191 5675365
Fax: 0191 5671276
Email: enquiries@durhamfreemasons.org
© Copyright Durham Freemasons. All rights reserved 2020.
Webmaster: webmaster@durhamfreemasons.org
Important COVID-19 update from the Provincial Grand Master - Local Restrictions: 'click here'
×
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Necessary
Always Enabled
